Hey. So we saw
a new billboard.
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
What better way to announce
our new slightly lower prices
than with an ad campaign?
And what better face
for an ad campaign
than our new regional manager?
How'd it look?
You've seen it, right?
No.
Andy, somebody
defaced it.
What? How?
Morning, Stanley.
There's this thing
that people tend
to do with billboards.
How do I put this?
If there's an opportunity
for a graffiti artist
to work in a phallic shape
interacting
with the artwork,
it'll happen.
And Andy gave them
that opportunity.
Erin, how long did we order
those billboards for?
Six months.
Oh, God.
I need you to call
the billboard company.
Great billboard. Funny, edgy,
right up to the line
without crossing it. Loved it.
Which one did you see?
Washington Street.
The one with like
20 dongs on it.
Okay. Don't be gross.
What's going on?
Somebody defaced
the billboards
we just put out
in an inappropriate way.
That's funny.
Wait, from
the photo shoot
with you and me?
Yeah, Dwight.
No. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no. No!
Schrute Farms
is very easy to find.
It's right in the middle
of the root
vegetable district.
If the soil starts
to get acidic,
you've probably
gone too far.
Just give us the address,
we'll look it up online.
It's simpler this way.
It's really not.
Now,
stated arrival time
is 3:00 p.m.
I don't get the reason
for this party.
Yeah. What's the reason?
What's the reason, Andy?
What's the reason?
It's just
a garden party.
Sheesh!
You don't need a reason
to throw a garden party
any more than you
need a reason
to throw a birthday party.
It's a garden party.
You don't need a reason.
A few other super
simple reminders.
No burping, no slurping.
When eating, take small bites
and chew thoroughly
with your mouth closed.
Yes, Darryl?
What happens when
we're done chewing?
Do we spit it out on the floor
or keep it in our mouths
the rest of the time?
I get it. I'm being
a little overbearing.
But I promise to be
under-bearing for a week
if you guys just
all step it up.
Andy, we understand
basic table manners.
We're not children.
Yeah. It's just
a picnic.
This is not a picnic, Phyllis.
It's a garden party.
There's a grill
in the warehouse
I could bring.
Oh, ew.
Please don't.
Not a barbeque.
It's better than a barbeque.
It's dignified. Quieter.
There are rules.
How is that better
than a barbeque?
What's the dress
code on this?
I'm glad you asked.
Connecticut casual.
Any chance Connecticut casual
is Pennsylvania business?
I.E., this is what
I'm wearing to your party.
Guys, my family just threw
a garden party to celebrate
my brother's promotion.
It was a huge success.
Check it out.
There's a video online.
Heartwarming impromptu
father/son duet.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Oscar,
you showed me this.
I've seen this.
That's not you.
Yeah. Who's the sausage?
It's my dad
and my brother.
I would have joined in,
but this melody
doesn't really support
another harmony part, so...
Check it out.
That's my brother's boss.
Look how psyched he is.
He's having an awesome time.
Ah.
And did Robert California
get an invite to your party?
Yeah, of course.
I mean, yeah,
I think he did.
Why didn't you just say
this was to impress
Robert California?
I cannot believe that Andy
is throwing a party like this
just to impress the CEO.
Classic Gabe move.
Hey, Andy, how about
you don't steal
my business strategies
and I won't dress like my life
is just one long brunch.
See you all there
at 3:00 p.m.
Connecticut casual.
Remember your manners
and have a wonderful time.
And please refer to the map.
Stay off of the web.
Thank you.
So, we've typed in
the address.
Now let's take a look
at the street view.
They don't warn you when
the cameras are driving by.
Ah.
Why do you keep reading
that garden party book?
I mean, how hard are
finger sandwiches and tea?
There's so much
more to it than that.
I've been wanting
Schrute Farms to break into
the high-end event
hosting industry
for some time,
and this party is
a great opportunity.
Plus, I've got
a secret weapon.
Only one copy
in the world,
and some sucker
on the Internet
sold it to me for $2.
I'm actually really
disappointed in how poorly
my book is doing.
I've only sold one copy.
Is there anything you wish
you'd done differently
to avoid cankles?
Nope.
I've already gone up
another cup size.
The senator
is grossed out.
When do you start
feeling it kick?
Cece was around 22 weeks,
but Philip was much earlier.
Philip?
Oh, my gosh. Yes.
But don't say
anything, okay?
It's after my grandfather.
Philip is the name
that we're using.
It's after my favorite cat.
Oh, wow.
Funny. It's after
my grandfather.
It's after my cat.
Andrew, I picked up
two possible gifts
to bring this afternoon.
One, a pot of marmalade.
Ooh, that sounds great.
That is
what you want then?
The marmalade?
Sure.
You don't want
to hear the other one.
You love marmalade?
I'll hear the other one.
It's a basil plant.
You know, the marmalade
sounds great.
I also mentioned
the marmalade to my sister,
and she's very interested.
Then the basil will be fine.
Well, you clearly want
the marmalade.
Gretchen, I need
another marmalade.
All right.
Hey, where do I park?
I'm the valet.
You have to give me
your car. I'm parking.
I can probably park it myself.
I'm the valet. You have
to give me your car.
It's probably okay
that I park...
No. I think
it's probably
better that I...
I'm the valet.
You have to give me...
It's a finicky car.
Get out of your car.
Get out.
Have a good time
at the thing.
It's a little tricky.
You might want to...
Mr. Ryan Howard!
"Chapter Two.
Announcing guests
as they enter
"is the height of decorum.
"The more volume displayed,
the more honor is bestowed
upon everyone present."
Stanley Hudson
and his mistress Cynthia!
James, Pamela
and Peepee Halpert!
How's it going
over here, guys?
Andy, stop hovering.
You're being
really annoying.
Didn't mean
to bother you, Mable.
"Mable, Mable,
if you're able,
"keep your elbows
off the table."
Wow.
Mr. and Mrs. Walter
and Ellen Bernard!
So you all work
with Andy?
Well, technically, for Andy.
Technically,
for Robert California.
He's our CEO.
I thought you
were the CEO.
I don't know how
you got there.
You said you were
running the company.
This branch.
I'm the regional manager.
Yes. Well, that makes
more sense.
Are you all
regional managers?
Did I throw this party
to impress my parents?
That's crazy.
No, if they wanted
a garden party, they could
throw one themselves.
Which, as a matter of fact,
they did last week.
They threw one
for my baby brother,
and it was totally amazing.
But I couldn't care less.
Can I introduce
you around now?
Yeah, we don't have too long.
We have theater tickets.
What are you
going to see?
Moneyball.
It was
Walter Jr.'s choice.
There he is.
What?
Bro-nard.
I didn't know you were
going to be here.
I wouldn't have missed it.
Okay.
Ahh!
I'm Walter. I'm Andy's
younger brother.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm Jim.
Tuna, right?
And this must be
your lovely wife, Pam.
No.
Hell no.
She wishes.
No, no, no,
no, no. No.
Sir, I need to be able
to feed all the guests.
I understand.
Excuse me.
Set that down.
Present yourself.
"Chapter Four.
One of the host's
most important duties
"is as dance master.
"A proper courtly dance
sets the tone
for the entire afternoon."
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I present
Robert California!
Hello, Andy.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Hey, I want you to meet
my first bosses,
Mom and Dad.
Yes. Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Pleasure.
Andy, where shall I put
your basil plant?
I thought you were
going to bring
the marmalade?
No. I'm certain
you said basil.
This is not funny, man.
Let me down.
I think this thing is broken.
It's not broken, Kevin.
This is how it works.
It's so pretty today.
It's getting chilly.
Yeah. We really
should be leaving.
Yeah. Um...
It'll be weird if the boss-man
didn't make a toast,
so hang on.
Everybody, I just want
to take this opportunity
to thank you all for coming,
and to raise a glass
to my amazing staff.
Toasts are great.
I mean, you toast somebody,
they toast you back.
It just goes round and round.
That's my favorite part
about toasts, the reciprocity.
Let's hear from you guys.
Who do you want to toast?
Yeah, I'll say something.
I think we should be
acknowledging our boss
because none of us
would be here without him.
Robert California.
To Robert.
Yay, Robert!
I cannot believe I didn't
think of toasting Robert.
Get in the game, Gabriel.
Why are you talking
to Stanley's mistress?
I would like to toast
someone who isn't here,
but who will be
in just four short months.
Welcome to the world,
Philip Lipton.
Aww.
I also would like
to toast Philip Halpert,
who's due even sooner.
May he be a good namesake
to my grandfather,
who I promised as a child,
long before tonight,
that I would one day
name my son after him.
To Philip Halpert.
To Philip.
All right.
She just always has
to copy anything I do.
It's the Ford Taurus
situation all over again.
I'd like to make
a toast to the troops.
Here, here.
Yes.
All the troops.
Both sides.
I think
we should toast...
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Last Supper.
"Chapter Nine.
The tableau vivant
is not only welcome,
"but expected entertainment
at any garden party."
Andy?
I think that we should
acknowledge the man
who has led us to such
a profitable quarter.
To Robert California.
Yeah!
I would also like
to toast Robert California.
Mr. California...
You can't triple
toast somebody.
At least not until
we hit everyone once.
I'll say a few words
if that's all right
with you, Andy.
Yeah.
You people say I led you,
but it wasn't me.
You want to toast the man
who led you to success,
but the boss is irrelevant.
Andy and I
produce nothing.
We do nothing.
We sit in our offices
and demand,
"I want this
and that right now"
like petulant children.
You know the difference
between a crying baby
and a manager?
One day the baby
will grow up.
But without you, Andy and I
would be sitting in
our dirty diapers
waiting for someone
to change us, wipe us.
I should be toasting you,
thanking you,
for allowing me to have
the easiest job
in the universe.
Cheers.
To Robert California.
From the moment
you entered our building
and our hearts, you...
Some of you know that we have
an Internet star in our midst.
Mr. Walter Banes Bernard, Sr.,
please report to the stage.
I'm eating, Andy.
Come on.
Okay. All right.
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah, what do you
want to do?
Well, how about
one of our classic
father/son duets?
Oh, whoa.
You sure?
Really?
It's a little tricky.
Saying I love you
Is not the words
It's too high. It's high
but it's not that high.
Really?
Right. It feels strained.
Yeah. Just take it down.
Saying I love...
Saying I love you
Here. Just give it
to me. Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Something like...
Saying I love you
is not the word...
You don't come in yet.
...I want to hear from you
It's not that I want you
Not to say
but if you only knew
More than words
Is all you have to do
to make it real
Is anyone filming this?
Seriously. Erin!
It's either taping
or calling.
What would you do
If my heart was torn in two
You know what?
Walter Jr. is here.
Why don't you come up
and join us?
WALTER, JR.: Yeah, no.
No, come up and do
something with me.
I don't know, Pop.
I'm just having a good time
getting to know
Andy's friends here.
Get up there and sing,
or I will cut your larynx
and you'll never be
able to sing again.
Whoo! Come on!
Come on.
Give them what they want.
All right. This old thing.
I don't even...
May the good Lord be with you
Down every road you roam
And may sunshine and happiness
Surround you when
you're far from home
And may you grow to be proud
Dignified and true
And do unto others
As you'd have done to you
Cheers! All right.
What's going on?
Cheers, cheers.
Get your own guitar.
Sorry.
Please
hang up and try again.
I am so cold.
It's because you
didn't bring a jacket.
My first love is beet farming,
but it's a young man's game.
Whoever heard of
an old beet farmer?
Forget the beets.
Concentrate on the hosting.
I can spend a considerable
amount of money
having my birthday party here.
Really? We have a number
of birthday packages.
The Pewter package
has the least amount
of goats.
It's not no goats,
it's still 10 to 12 goats,
depending on the
availability of the goats.
Now the goat package,
obviously, has the most goats.
What were you thinking?
Of course I am not
interested in goats.
Why would you spend
so much time going over
the goats with me?
I can get you
exotic meats.
Hippo steaks.
Giraffe burgers.
We'll talk.
It'll all be goat.
Hello, Cece Halpert.
This is Andrew Bernard.
I'd very much like
to speak with you about
your paper supply needs.
That wasn't even
my worst sales call.
Hi.
What was that display?
I don't know.
I just thought
if I could throw
this great garden party
and show you
how respected I am,
that you'd be proud of me.
Andrew.
I know.
I know that you're
proud of me.
I'm not going to tell you
how impressed I am
that you're a manager
of some rinky-dink branch
of a paper company
in Scranton, Pennsylvania.
How long are you
going to go on
needing my approval?
You're a grown man.
Don't act like
a little boy who needs...
I think if I had
parents like that,
I'd be trying to convince
everyone all the time
how great I was, too.
Guess we found
Andy's Rosebud.
Rosebud?
It's a reference
to Citizen Kane.
Something that explains
why a person became
the way they are.
I know Citizen Kane.
Rosebud didn't explain
why he was how he was.
It just represented what was
important to him as a child,
that he missed.
Different school of thought.
Let's just agree to disagree.
No. You're wrong.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm too hot anyway.
My body has somehow
become acclimated
to southern Italy.
Isn't that strange?
I've never been there.
Oh! Ah. Well.
Yes, that's nice.
Thank you.
It was a nice party.
The setting was
a little strange. The food...
Sandwiches were dry.
Bye, Tuna.
Bye, Pam!
Hey, everybody,
I'm going to leave,
and I just wanted to say
I'm really sorry.
Cheeseburger
or hamburger?
Um...
Cheeseburger.
Nard-Dog.
Thanks, Oscar.
What are they doing?
Closing ceremonies.
Nice touch.
I think I left my wallet
in your house.
Who cares?
Right here.
Mr. James Halpert!
Keys. My keys.
Stop forgetting things.
I didn't forget them.
They're right here.
Mr. James Halpert!
I'm so sorry.
I think I forgot the...
What...
You idiot.
Ooh.
Mis...
Mi...
What are you doing?
Hey, I have a question.
Who do you think
is really the best salesman
in this office?
Stupid question, obviously...
Mr. James Halpert!